New York State Labor Documentation Project on Microfilm 5787 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Labor Documentation Project on Microfilm
1918-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
5787 mf
44.11 cubic feet
397 microfilm reels
Records (documents), microfilm.
This collection consists of Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project Union Label Series I-Series III
5706183
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 16, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, a joint project of NYU's Tamiment Library and the New York City Central Labor Council, is committed to preserving the history of the labor movement and labor history of the New York area.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project Union Label Series I-Series III:
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project Central Trades & Labor Council 4 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation 4A's
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Actors Equity 21 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project IBEW, Local 3 26 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project History or Local 463, IUE 7 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project AFSCME-Dist. Council 37 Minutes 1 box
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project Civil Service Forum 14 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 8 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project A.G.M.A. 49 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project Local 153 OPEIU 8 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project A.P.W.U. Bklyn Local 2 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project United Scenic Artist 15 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 11 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State 9 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Project Local 802 79 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, N.Y. Labor Documentation Center Carpenters Local 532, Elmira, NY 5 boxes
Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, New York University, District 65, U.A.W. Minutes 19 boxes
The Civil Service Leader 18 boxes
along with other labor archives material.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arrangement
Series Subject Files, 1941-2001
Series Legal Files, 1974-1979, 1981-1983:
Series 1: Minutes, 1947-88
Sub-Series General Membership Meeting Minutes, 1947-74, 1979-88 Sub-Series Executive Board Meeting Minutes, 1950-56, 1960-88
Series 2: Subject Files, 1946-49, 1951-52, 1955, 1959, 1961-88.
Series 3: Utica Graphic Communications Local No. 58-C, GCIU Subject Files, 1941, 1946, 1950-53, 1957, 1959-86
Series City Teacher's Association of Schenectady, 1918-34, 1937-43
Series Schenectady Federation of Teachers, AFT Local 803, 1942-89
Series 1: Minutes, 1944-89
Series 2: Subject Files, 1944-80, 1982-85, 1987
Actors' Equity Association.; AFL-CIO. New York City Central labor Council.; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); Allied Printing Trader Council (New York (State)); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Local 340.; American Federation of Musicians. Local 802.; American Guild of Musical Artists.; American Postal Workers Union, Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Associated Actors and Artistes of America.; CIO Council (New York, N.Y.); Civil Service Forum.; Communications Workers of America. Local 1150.; International Association of Machinists. Eureka Lodge 434.; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Local no. 3 (New York, N.Y.); International Typographical Union. No. 6 (New York, N.Y.); International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers. Local 463 (New York, N.Y.); Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.); Musical Mutual Protective Union; New York Industrial Union Council, CIO; Office and Professional Employees International Union.; Office and Professional Employees International Union. Local 153 (New York, N.Y.); Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives; Teachers' Union of the City of New York; Union Label.; United Federation of Teachers; United Hatters, Cap, and Millinery Workers International Union.
5706183
- Union Label - Series I, Box 1, 1918-1932 (Reel 5001)
  Scope and Contents
  Union Label Advocate - 1918-1932
- Union Label, Box I: Series II: Union Label Store, 1920-1947 (Reel 5002)
- Union Label Box II: Series III: Central Union Label Council and Executive Committee, 1911-1924 (Reel 5003)
- Union Label - Series III, box 2, 1925-1933 (Reel 5004)
  Central Union Label Council and Executive Committee 1925-1933
- Union Label - Series III, box 2, 1934-1941 (Reel 5005)
  Central Union Label Council and Executive Committee 1934-1941
- Union Label - Series III, box 3, 1942-1955 (Reel 5006)
  Central Union Label Council and Executive Committee 1942-1955
- Union Label - Series III, box 3, 1939-1962 (Reel 5007)
  Central Union Label Council and Executive Committee 1956-1962 and Series Iv, box 3 - Union Label Trades Dept., AFL- CIO Oct. 1939-Dec. 1946
- Union Label - box 1, Series I, 1938-1948 (Reel 5008)
  Records in Yiddish 1938-1948
- Union Label - Series I, box 1, 1949-1956 (Reel 5009)
  Jewish Labor Committee - Records in Yiddish 1949-1956
- Union Label - box 1, Series I, 1957-1969 (Reel 5010)
  Records in Yiddish 1957-1969
- Union Label - box 2, Series II, 1964-1978 (Reel 5011)
  Records in English 1964-1978
- Union Label - box 2, Series II, 1940-1970 (Reel 5012)
  Records in English 1966-1970 and Series III - Translations Yiddish to English 1940-1949
- Central Trades & Labor Council - box 1, 1933-1937 (Reel 5013)
  Minutes, Regular & Executive Board 1933-1937
- Central Trades & Labor Council - box 1, 1938-1941 (Reel 5014)
  Minutes, Regular & Executive Board 1938-1941
- Central Trades & Labor Council - box 2, 1942-1949 (Reel 5015)
  Minutes, Regular Meetings; Minutes, Executive Board 1942-1949
- Central Trades & Labor Council - box 2, box 3, 1950-1956 (Reel 5016)
  Minutes, Executive Board 1950 - Minutes, Regular & Executive Board 1951-1956
- Central Trades & Labor Council - box 3, box 4, 1957-1975 (Reel 5017)
  Minutes Regular & Executive Board 1957-1958 - Minutes, Executive Board 1959-1975
- Central Trades & Labor Council - box 4, 1959-1982 (Reel 5018)
  Minutes Executive Board 1976-1982 Minutes, Delegates Meeting 1959-1969
- Central Trades & Labor Council AFL-CIO - box 4, 1970-1982 (Reel 5019)
  Minutes Delegates Meetings 1970-1982
- 4A's, 1919-1938 (Reel 5020)
  Minutes Folder July 1919-December 1938
- 4A's, 1939 (Reel 5021)
  Minutes folder 1939
- 4A's, 1940-1948 (Reel 5022)
  Minutes folder 1940-1948
- 4A's, 1949 (Reel 5023)
  Minutes Folder 1949
- 4A's, 1950-1954 (Reel 5024)
  Minutes Folder 1950-1954
- 4A's, 1956-1965 (Reel 5025)
  Minutes Folder 1956-1965
- 4A's, 1966-1972 (Reel 5026)
  Minutes Folder 1966-1972
- 4A's, 1973-1977 (Reel 5027)
  Minutes Folder 1973-1977
- 4A's, 1978-1982 (Reel 5028)
  Minutes Folder 1978-1982
- 4A's, 1919-1925 (Reel 5029)
  Council Meetings Minutes 1919-1925
- Actors Equite - box 1, 1915-1917 (Reel 5030)
  Council Meetings Minutes 1915-1917
- Actors Equity - box 1, 1918-1919 (Reel 5031)
  Council Meetings Minutes 1918-1919
- Actors Equity - box 1, 1920-1922 (Reel 5032)
  Council Meetings Minutes 1920-1922
- Actor Equity - box 1, 1922-1923 (Reel 5033)
  Council Meetings Minutes 1922-1923
- Actors Equity - box 2, 1924-1925 (Reel 5034)
  Council meeting Minutes 1924-1925
- Actors Equity - box 2, 1926-1927 (Reel 5035)
  Council Meeting Minutes 1926-1927
- Actors Equity box 2, 1928-1929 (Reel 5036)
  Council Meeting Minutes 1928-1929
- Actors Equity - box 3, 1929-1937 (Reel 5037)
  1929-1937
- Actors Equity - box 3, 1929-1937 (Reel 5038)
  1929-1927
- Actors Equity - box 3, 1935-1937 (Reel 5039)
  1935-1937
- Actors Equity - box 4, 1938 (Reel 5040)
  Council Meetings Minutes 1938
- Actors Equity - box 4, 1939-1940 (Reel 5041)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1939-1940
- Actors Equity - box 4, 1941-1942 (Reel 5042)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1941-1942
- Actors Equity - box 5, 1944-1946 (Reel 5043)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1944-1946
- Actors Equity - box 5, 1947 (Reel 5044)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1947
- Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes - Box 5, 1948 (Reel 5044A)
- Actors Equity - box 6, 1949 (Reel 5045)
  Council Meeting Minutes 1949
- Actors Equity - box 6, 1950 (Reel 5046)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1950
- Actors Equity - box 6, 1951 (Reel 5047)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1951
- Actors Equity - box 7, 1952 (Reel 5048)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1952
- Actors Equity - box 7, 1953 (Reel 5049)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1953
- Actors Equity: box 7, 1954 (Reel 5050)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1954
- Actors Equity - box 8, 1955 (Reel 5051)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1955
- Actors Equity - box 8, 1956 (Reel 5052)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1956
- Actors Equity - box 9, 1957 (Reel 5053)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1957
- Actors Equity - box 9, 1958 (Reel 5054)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1958
- Actors Equity - box 9, 1959 (Reel 5055)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1959
- Actors Equity - box 10, 1960 (Reel 5056)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1960
- Actors Equity - box 10, 1961 (Reel 5057)
  Actors Equity Council Meeting Minutes 1961
- Actors Equity - box 11, 1962 (Reel 5058)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1962
- Actors Equity - box 11, 1962 (Reel 5059)
- Actors Equity - box 11, 1963 (Reel 5060)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1963
- Actors Equity - box 11, 1963 (Reel 5061)
- Actors Equity - box 12, 1964 (Reel 5062)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1964
- Actors Equity - box 12, 1964 (Reel 5063)
- Actors Equity - box 13, 1965 (Reel 5064)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1965
- Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes - box 13, 1966 (Reel 5065)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1966
- Actors Equity - box 14, 1967 (Reel 5066)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1967
- Actors Equity - box 14, 1968 (Reel 5067)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1968
- Actors Equity - box 14, 1968 (Reel 5068)
- Actors Equity - box 15, 1969 (Reel 5069)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1969
- Actors Equity - box 15, 1969 (Reel 5070)
- Actors Equity - box 15, 1970 (Reel 5071)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1970
- Actors Equity - box 15, 1970 (Reel 5072)
  Actors Equity Councils Meetings Minutes 1970
- Actors Equity - box 16, 1971 (Reel 5073)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1971
- Actors Equity - box 16, 1971 (Reel 5074)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minute 1971
- Actors Equity - box 16, 1972 (Reel 5075)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1972
- Actors Equity - box 16, 1972 (Reel 5076)
- Actors Equity - box 17, 1973 (Reel 5077)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1973
- Actors Equity - box 17, 1973 (Reel 5078)
- Actors Equity - box 17, 1974 (Reel 5079)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1974
- Actors Equity - box 17, 1974 (Reel 5080)
- Actors Equity - box 18, 1975 (Reel 5081)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1975
- Actors Equity - box 18, 1975 (Reel 5082)
- Actors Equity - box 18, 1976 (Reel 5083)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1976
- Actors Equity - box 18, 1976 (Reel 5084)
- Actors Equity - box 19, 1977 (Reel 5085)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1977
- Actors Equity - box 19, 1977 (Reel 5086)
- Actors Equity - box 19, 1978 (Reel 5087)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1978
- Actors Equity - box 19, 1978 (Reel 5088)
- Actors Equity - box 19, 1978 (Reel 5089)
- Actors Equity - box 20, 1979 (Reel 5090)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1979
- Actors Equity - box 20, 1979 (Reel 5091)
- Actors Equity - box 20, 1979 (Reel 5092)
- Actors Equity - box 20, 1980 (Reel 5093)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1980
- Actors Equity - box 20, 1980 (Reel 5094)
- Actors Equity - box 20, 1980 (Reel 5095)
- Actors Equity - box 21, 1981 (Reel 5096)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1981
- Actors Equity - box 21, 1981 (Reel 5097)
- Actors Equity - box 21, 1982 (Reel 5098)
  Actors Equity Council Meetings Minutes 1982
- Actors Equity - box 21, 1982 (Reel 5099)
- Actors Equity - box 21, 1918-1924 (Reel 5100)
  Actors Equity Executive Committee Minutes 1918-1924
- IBEW, Local 3 - vol. 1/1-1/5, 1901-1906 (Reel 5101)
  1901-1906
- IBEW, Local 3 - vol. 1/6, 1908 (Reel 5102)
- IBEW, Local 3 - vol. 1/7-1/9, 1908 (Reel 5103)
- IBEW, Local 3 - vol. 1/10, 2/1-2/3, 1909-1911 (Reel 5104)
- IBEW, Local 3 - vol. 2/4-2/9, 1912-1914 (Reel 5105)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1915-1919 (Reel 5106)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1920-1922 (Reel 5107)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1923-1931 (Reel 5108)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1932-1938 (Reel 5109)
  Regular Membership
- IBEW, Local 3, 1939-1941 (Reel 5110)
  Executive Board
- IBEW, Local 3, 1942-1943 (Reel 5111)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1944-1946 (Reel 5112)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1947-1950 (Reel 5113)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1951-1953 (Reel 5114)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1954-1955 (Reel 5115)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1956-1957 (Reel 5116)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1958-1959 (Reel 5117)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1960-1962 (Reel 5118)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1962-1965 (Reel 5119)
  Regular Membership & Executive Board
- IBEW, Local 3, 1966-1967 (Reel 5120)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1968-1970 (Reel 5121)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1971-1972 (Reel 5122)
  Executive Board & Regular Membership
- IBEW, Local 3, 1973-1974 (Reel 5123)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1975-1977 (Reel 5124)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1978-1980 (Reel 5125)
- IBEW, Local 3, 1981-1982 (Reel 5126)
- History or Local 463, IUE - box 1, vol 1, 1951-1959 (Reel 5127)
- History of Local 463, IUE - box 1, vol. 2, 1960-1965 (Reel 5128)
- History of Local 463, IUE - box 1, vol 2, pt. 2, 1966-1969 (Reel 5129)
- History of Local 463, IUE - box 1, vol. 3, pt. 1, 1970-1973 (Reel 5130)
- History of Local 463, IUE - box 2, vol. 3, pt. 2, 1974-1976 (Reel 5131)
- History of Local 463, IUE - box 2, vol. 3, pt. 3, 1977-1979 (Reel 5132)
- History of Local 463, IUE - box 2, vol. 4, pt. 1, 1980-1985 (Reel 5133)
- AFSCME-Dist. Council 37 Minutes, 1959-1968 (Reel 5134)
- Civil Service Forum - vol. 1, 1931-1933 (Reel 5135)
  Minutes
- Civil Service Forum - vol. 2, 1934-1936 (Reel 5136)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.3, 1937-1939 (Reel 5137)
- Civil Service Forum - vol. 4, 1940-1942 (Reel 5138)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.5, 1942-1946 (Reel 5139)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.6, 1947-1949 (Reel 5140)
- Civil Service Forum - vol. 1, box 2, 1950-1951 (Reel 5141)
- Civil Service Forum - vol. 2, box 2, 1952-1954 (Reel 5142)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.3, box 2, 1955-1960 (Reel 5143)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.4, box 2, 1961-1968 (Reel 5144)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.5, box 2, 1943-1950 (Reel 5145)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.5, box 2, 1943-1950 (Reel 5146)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.6, bx 2, 1951-1960 (Reel 5147)
- Civil Service Forum - vol.7, box 2, 1961-1968 (Reel 5147)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol. 1-2, 1896-1904 (Reel 5148)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol. 3-4, 1904-1913 (Reel 5149)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol. 5-9, 1914-1926 (Reel 5150)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol. 10-13, 1917-1932 (Reel 5151)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol. 14, 1933-1938 (Reel 5152)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol.15, 1939-1944 (Reel 5153)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol. 16, 1945-1949 (Reel 5154)
- ITU N.Y. Mailers Local 6 - vol. 17, 1950-1954 (Reel 5155)
- A.G.M.A. - box 1, 1936-1939 (Reel 5156)
- A.G.M.A. - box 1, 1940-1942 (Reel 5157)
- A.G.M.A. - box 1-2, 1943-1944 (Reel 5158)
- A.G.M.A. - Box 2, 1944-1945 (Reel 5159)
- A.G.M.A. - box 2, 1946 (Reel 5160)
- A.G.M.A. - box 3, 1946-1947 (Reel 5161)
- A.G.M.A. - box 3, 1947 (Reel 5162)
- A.G.M.A. - box 4, 1948 (Reel 5163)
- A.G.M.A. - box 4, 1948 (Reel 5164)
- A.G.M.A. - box 4, 1949-1950 (Reel 5165)
- A.G.M.A. - box 5, 1950 (Reel 5166)
- A.G.M.A. - box 6, 1951 (Reel 5167)
- A.G.M.A. - box 6-7, 1952 (Reel 5168)
- A.G.M.A. - box 7, 1953 (Reel 5169)
- A.G.M.A. - box 7, 1954 (Reel 5170)
- A.G.M.A. - box 8, 1955 (Reel 5171)
- A.G.M.A. - box 8, 1956 (Reel 5172)
- A.G.M.A. - box 9, 1957 (Reel 5173)
- A.G.M.A. - box 9, 1958 (Reel 5174)
- A.G.M.A. - box 10, 1959 (Reel 5175)
- A.G.M.A. - box 10-11, 1959-1960 (Reel 5176)
- A.G.M.A. - box 9, 1960 (Reel 5177)
- A.G.M.A. - box 11, 1961 (Reel 5178)
- A.G.M.A. - box 12, 1961-1962 (Reel 5179)
- A.G.M.A. - box 12, 1962 (Reel 5180)
- A.G.M.A. - box 13, 1963 (Reel 5181)
- A.G.M.A. - box 13, 1963-1964 (Reel 5182)
- A.G.M.A. - box 14, 1964-1965 (Reel 5183)
- A.G.M.A. - box 14, 1965 (Reel 5184)
- A.G.M.A. - box 15, 1966 (Reel 5185)
- A.G.M.A. - box 15, 1966-1967 (Reel 5186)
- A.G.M.A. - box 15, 1967 (Reel 5187)
- A.G.M.A. - box 16, 1968 (Reel 5188)
- A.G.M.A. - box 17, 1969 (Reel 5189)
- A.G.M.A. - box 17, 1970 (Reel 5190)
- A.G.M.A. - box 18, 1971 (Reel 5191)
- A.G.M.A. - box 18, 1972 (Reel 5192)
- A.G.M.A. - box 18-19, 1973 (Reel 5193)
- A.G.M.A. - box 19, 1974 (Reel 5194)
- A.G.M.A. - box 19-20, 1975 (Reel 5195)
- A.G.M.A. - box 20, 1976 (Reel 5196)
- A.G.M.A. - box 20, 1977 (Reel 5197)
- A.G.M.A. - box 20, 1978 (Reel 5198)
- A.G.M.A. - box 21, 1979 (Reel 5199)
- A.G.M.A. - box 21, 1980 (Reel 5200)
- A.G.M.A. - box 22, 1948 (Reel 5201)
- A.G.M.A. - box 23, 1949 (Reel 5202)
- A.G.M.A. - box 23, 1950 (Reel 5203)
- A.G.M.A. - box 23, 1962 (Reel 5204)
- Local 153 OPEIU, 1958-1961 (Reel 5205)
  Executive Board Minutes
- Local 153 OPEIU, 1962-1969 (Reel 5206)
  Executive Board Members
- Local 153 OPEIU, 1970-1981 (Reel 5207)
- Local 153 OPEIU - box 1, 1941-1950 (Reel 5208)
  Minutes AFOE - 1941-1946; Local 153 Minutes 1947-1950
- Local 153 OPEIU - box 1, 1951-1965 (Reel 5209)
- Local 153 OPEIU - box 1, 1961-1965 (Reel 5210)
- Local 153 OPEIU - box 2, 1973-1980 (Reel 5211)
- Local 153 OPEIU - box 2, 1973-1980 (Reel 5212)
- A.P.W.U. - Brooklyn Local - box 1, 1918-1950 (Reel 5213)
- A.P.W.U. - Brooklyn Local - box 1, box 2, 1951-1977 (Reel 5214)
- United Scenic Artist - box 1, 1918-1922 (Reel 5215)
- United Scenic Artist - box 1, 1923-1926 (Reel 5216)
- United Scenic Artist - box 1, 1927-1930 (Reel 5217)
- United Scenic Artist - box 1, 1931-1933 (Reel 5218)
- United Scenic Artist - box 2, 1934-1936 (Reel 5219)
- United Scenic Artist - box 2, 1937-1939 (Reel 5220)
- United Scenic Artist - box 2, 1940-1941 (Reel 5221)
- United Scenic Artist - box 2, 1942-1944 (Reel 5222)
- United Scenic Artist - box 3, 1945-1949 (Reel 5223)
- United Scenic Artist - box 3, 1950-1955 (Reel 5224)
- United Scenic Artist - box 4, 1956-1963 (Reel 5225)
- United Scenic Artist - box 4, 1964-1967 (Reel 5226)
- United Scenic Artist - box 3, 1968-1970 (Reel 5227)
- United Scenic Artist - box 5, 1971-1973 (Reel 5228)
- United Scenic Artist - box 6, 1974-1975 (Reel 5229)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 1, 1908-1932 (Reel 5230)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 1, 1932-1954 (Reel 5231)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 1, 1954-1962 (Reel 5232)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 1, 1973-1977 (Reel 5233)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 2, 1894-1902 (Reel 5234)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 2, 1902-1909 (Reel 5235)
  Regular meetings
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 3, 1911-1924 (Reel 5236)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 3, 1924-1936 (Reel 5237)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 4, 1937-1953 (Reel 5238)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 4, 1953-1962 (Reel 5239)
- IAM, Eureka Lodge 434 - box 4, 1962-1977 (Reel 5240)
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 1, 1897-1938 (Reel 5241)
  Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 1, 1938-1943 (Reel 5242)
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 1, 1944-1948 (Reel 5243)
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 1, 1949-1954 (Reel 5244)
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 1, box 2, 1954-1961 (Reel 5245)
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 2, 1961-1970 (Reel 5246)
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 2, 1971-1985 (Reel 5247)
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 1, 1925-1943 (Reel 5248)
  ACTWU-Local 340 Retail Clothing Salesman
- Allied Printing Trades Council of New York State - box 2, 1947-1975 (Reel 5249)
- Local 802 -, 1922-1923 (Reel 5257)
  Minutes of Governing (Executive) Board
- Local 802 -, 1927-1928 (Reel 5258)
- Local 802 -, 1927-1928 (Reel 5259)
- Local 802 -, 1929-1930 (Reel 5260)
  Minutes of the Executive Board
- Local 802 -, 1931-1932 (Reel 5261)
- Local 802 -, 1933-1934 (Reel 5262)
- Local 802 -, 1935 (Reel 5263)
- Local 802 -, 1936 (Reel 5264)
- Local 802 -, 1937 (Reel 5265)
- Local 802 -, 1938 (Reel 5266)
- Local 802 -, 1939 (Reel 5267)
- Local 802 -, 1940 (Reel 5268)
- Local 802 -, 1940-1941 (Reel 5269)
- Local 802 -, 1942 (Reel 5270)
- Local 802 -, 1942-1943 (Reel 5271)
- Local 802 -, 1943-1944 (Reel 5272)
- Local 802 -, 1944-1945 (Reel 5273)
  Minutes of the Executives Board
- Local 802 -, 1946 (Reel 5274)
- Local 802 -, 1947 (Reel 5275)
- Local 802 -, 1948 (Reel 5276)
- Local 802 -, 1949 (Reel 5277)
- Local 802 -, 1950 (Reel 5278)
- Local 802 -, 1951 (Reel 5279)
- Local 802 -, 1952 (Reel 5280)
- Local 802 -, 1953 (Reel 5281)
- Local 802 -, 1954 (Reel 5282)
  Minutes of the Executive Branch
- Local 802 -, 1954 (Reel 5283)
- Local 802 -, 1955 (Reel 5284)
- Local 802 -, 1955 (Reel 5285)
- Local 802 -, 1956 (Reel 5286)
- Local 802 -, 1956 (Reel 5287)
- Local 802 -, 1957 (Reel 5288)
- Local 802 -, 1957-1958 (Reel 5289)
- Local 802 -, 1959-1960 (Reel 5290)
- Local 802 -, 1960-1961 (Reel 5291)
- Local 802 -, 1962-1963 (Reel 5292)
- Local 802 -, 1964-1965 (Reel 5293)
- Local 802 -, 1966-1967 (Reel 5294)
- Local 802 -, 1968-1969 (Reel 5295)
- Local 802 -, 1970 (Reel 5296)
- Local 802 -, 1972-1973 (Reel 5297)
- Local 802 -, 1974-1975 (Reel 5298)
- Local 802 -, 1976-1977 (Reel 5299)
- Local 802 -, 1978-1979 (Reel 5300)
- Local 802 -, 1980 (Reel 5301)
- Local 802 -, 1981 (Reel 5302)
- Local 802 -, 1982 (Reel 5303)
- Local 802 -, 1983-1984 (Reel 5304)
- Local 802 -, 1922-1923 (Reel 5305)
  Minutes of the Trial Board
- Local 802 -, 1922-1923 (Reel 5306)
- Local 802 -, 1923-1924 (Reel 5307)
- Local 802 -, 1924-1926 (Reel 5308)
- Local 802 -, 1926-1927 (Reel 5309)
- Local 802 -, 1927-1929 (Reel 5310)
- Local 802 -, 1929-1930 (Reel 5311)
- Local 802 -, 1931-1932 (Reel 5312)
- Local 802 -, 1933-1934 (Reel 5313)
- Local 802 -, 1934-1935 (Reel 5314)
- Local 802 -, 1936-1937 (Reel 5315)
- Local 802 -, 1937-1938 (Reel 5316)
- Local 802 -, 1938-1939 (Reel 5317)
- Local 802 -, 1939-1940 (Reel 5318)
- Local 802 -, 1941 (Reel 5319)
- Local 802 -, 1942-1943 (Reel 5320)
- Local 802 -, 1943-1944 (Reel 5321)
- Local 802 -, 1945-1946 (Reel 5322)
- Local 802 -, 1947-1948 (Reel 5323)
- Local 802 -, 1949 (Reel 5324)
- Local 802 -, 1950-1951 (Reel 5325)
- Local 802 -, 1952-1953 (Reel 5326)
- Local 802 -, 1954-1955 (Reel 5327)
- Local 802 -, 1956-1957 (Reel 5328)
- Local 802 -, 1958 (Reel 5329)
- Local 802 -, 1960-1961 (Reel 5330)
- Local 802 -, 1961-1962 (Reel 5331)
- Local 802 -, 1962-1963 (Reel 5332)
- Local 802 -, 1963-1964 (Reel 5333)
- Local 802 -, 1965 (Reel 5334)
- Local 802 -, 1922-1940 (Reel 5335)
  Minutes of Regular Membership Meetings - Minutes of the Medical Board